trackmytime.com 2002-12-07

# TrackMyTime.com

This privacy statement covers the site www.TrackMyTime.com.  Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to our users’ privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices.

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact Avilin, LLC at 1-866-4AVILIN or email to [info@trackmytime.com](mailto:info@trackmytime.com).  
**  
Information Collection  
** Avilin, LLC is the sole owner of the information collected on www.TrackMyTime.com. Avilin, LLC collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

Registration

In order to use this Web site, a user must first complete the registration form.  During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which he has expressed interest.  Users are required to provide unique identifiers (such as, username and password), but may or may not provide other contact information.

We request information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).  This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders.  If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user.   Information Use   Profile  
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third parties to create a profile of our users.  A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences.  Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user’s visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them.  We do not share your profile with other third parties. **Cookies  
** A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user.  We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies.  For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates.  A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.  By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site.  If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site.  The only drawback to this is that the user will be need to sign on each time they visit the site.  Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.  See the “Profile” section. **

Log Files

** Like most standard Web site servers we use log files.  This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. **Communications from the Site  
** On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement.  For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email.  Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications.  However, these communications are not promotional in nature. **Customer Service**  
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the user’s wishes. **Sharing**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. **Third Party Intermediaries  
** We use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. **Business Transitions  
** In the event Avilin, LLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.  Users will be notified via prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the users’ personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section. **Links  
** This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Avilin, LLC, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.  We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.  This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. **Security** **  
** This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information.  When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL.  While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just ‘surfing’.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line.  All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices.  Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.  Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk.  When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to user information.  Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices.  Any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users’ information is protected.  Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, in a locked facility.

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to [info@trackmytime.com](mailto:info@trackmytime.com). **

Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

**

 **  
** If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ personally identifiable information. This can usually be done at the [member information page] **** or by emailing our Customer Support at info@trackmytime.com **.**   Or, contact us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. **Notification of Changes** **  
** If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.  If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner.  However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner.  In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. **

Contact Information

** **  
** If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:  
**  
1-866-4AVILIN  
3126 Milton Rd, Suite 209  
Charlotte, NC  28215
